

ABOUT

After completing my PhD in Robotics and Computer Science, I introduced my love of music and sound into my practice. I'm attracted by the technical aspect of sound and music, since I see all of these as inextricably linked and also love the creative side of technology and programming. In the last few years, I have specialized myself in web development and worked as a full-stack engineer.

CONTACT

- Granada (Spain)
- ✓ d.r.valeiras@gmail.com
- in LinkedIn profile
- pithub.com/valeiras

David Reverter Valeiras

Doctor of Engineering - Front End Developer

EDUCATION

PhD in Computer Science

Université Pierre et Marie Curie (Paris)

Master Degree in advanced Systems and Robotics

Université Pierre et Marie Curie (Paris)

Industrial Engineering, Specialty: Mechanics
E.T.S.E.I. de Vigo (Vigo)

Live Sound Technician

Centro de formación escénica de Andalucía

SKILLS

Programming languages:

TS	Typescript		JS	JavaScript	
덩	HTML		팅	CSS	
©	C++		ş	Python	
Tools:					
(js)	Node.js		₩	React	
N.	Next.js		•	Git	
∞	Arduino		 ★	Matlab	
Languages:					
Spanish		Native	English		Fluent
Galician		Native	French F		Fluent

EXPERIENCE

2023-2024: Full-stack developer

Ennubo (Madrid)

2022-2023: Developer of Mekanika

Cabeza Patata (London)

2020-2022: Live Sound Technician

Freelance

2017-2020: Professional musician

Freelance

2013-2017: Doctorate

Institut de la Vision (Paris)